27coupons.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy

* * *

  1. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our users. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit 27Coupons.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Please note that this policy applies only to 27Coupons.com and not to other companies' or organizations' websites to which we link.
  2. We may collect contact information from you when you use our site (for example, e-mail addresses, information from third party accounts like Gmail, Yahoomail etc).
  3. This information may be used to: 
    * Send news, information about our activities and general promotional material which we believe may be useful to you;
    * Operate and improve our site and services;
    * Process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
    * Respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
    * Link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.
  4. If you do not wish to have your personal information used in this manner or for any other specific purpose, please let us know.
  5. We utilise "cookies%u201D which enable us to monitor traffic patterns and to serve you more efficiently if you revisit the site. It is possible to enable your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This will provide you with an opportunity to accept or reject the cookie in each instance.
  6. We will not sell or otherwise provide your personal information to a third party, or make any other use of your personal information other than as follows: 
    * in an aggregated form that does not directly identify you;
    * with your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
    * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
    * (i) to comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of 27Coupons.com our agents, customers, community members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of 27Coupons.com employees, its customers, or any person;
    * in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
  7. You may request that we do not use your personal information or that we only use your personal information in certain ways.
  8. If we believe we have the legal requirement to do so, we will preserve the content of any email you send us.
  9. We may monitor your e-mail messages to us for troubleshooting or maintenance purposes or if we reasonably believe e-mail abuse may be occurring.
  10. We may collect personal information for analysis. In such circumstances we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that individuals remain anonymous.
  11. We use reasonable efforts to protect personal information which we collect (including your contact details. You will appreciate, however, that we cannot guarantee the security of transmission.
  12. You are entitled to have access to any personal information relating to you which you have previously supplied to us over this website. You are entitled to edit or delete such information unless we are required by law to retain it.
  13. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted here. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date below. If you have any queries or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.

  Last Updated: 14th May, 2013
